人生切割术
第二季 第十集[季终]
你记得你对我说的最后一句话吗
Do you remember the last thing that you said to me?
“她还活着”
"She's alive."
你完成冷港了吗
Have you finished Cold Harbor?
这里是什么地方
What is this place?
是生孩子用的木屋
It's a cabin for giving birth.
我为什么在这 你为什么在这
Why am I here? Why are you here?
冷港
Cold Harbor.
你完成了吗
Have you finished it?
没有
No.
那她还活着
Then she's still alive.
我们可以救她
We can save her.
谁
Who?
凯西女士
Ms. Casey.
珍玛
Gemma.
那里有一条走廊 和其他走廊不同
There's a hallway down there. It's different than the others.
它很长 很暗 是隐藏的
It's long and black and hidden.
欧文的画
From Irving's drawings.
什么
What?
里面有一部向下的电梯
With an elevator going down.
我们知道它在哪
We know where it is.
你在宴会上的演讲很有趣
What a funny speech you gave at the party.
之后我很生你气
I was cross with you after.
我朝你扔了一罐糖果
I threw a tin of candies.
天 你好奇怪
God, you're fucking weird.
我不爱我的女儿
I do not love my daughter.
我以前会在她身上看到基尔的影子
I used to see Kier in her,
但随着她长大 他的影子渐渐消失
but he left her as she grew.
听起来你这个爸爸很棒
You sound like a great dad.
我还有很多私生子
I sired others in the shadows.
但他们身上也没有他的影子
But he wasn't in them either.
直到我再一次看到他的身影
Until I saw him again.
在你身上
In you.
你和你的家族制造了人间地狱 你会在里面烧死
You and your family created hell, and you're going to burn in it.
这就是他
There he is.
明天是一个特别的日子
Tomorrow is a special day.
嘿
Hey!
你为什么来这里
Why did you come here?
你想要我干什么
What do you want from me?
所以 等等 我完成冷港后
So, wait, when I finish Cold Harbor,
他们会测试 然后就杀了她
they do a test, and then they kill her?
那个文件完成后 你必须尽快赶到黑长廊
Once that file is done, you'll need to quickly get to the black hallway,
然后下到测试楼层
then down to the testing floor.
你不完成那个文件 他们是不会让你离开宏观数据精检的
They'll not let you leave MDR till that file is complete.
好的 我到了下面要怎么找到她
Okay, but how do I find her once I'm down there?
你不会找到她的
No, you won't.
- 不会吗  - 对
- I won't? - No.
你的芯片只有你那一层的记忆
Your chip is only attuned to your floor.
你到了测试层时又会变成外面的自己
Once you get down to testing, you'll be your outie again.
然后他会找到珍玛 带她上到分离楼层
And then he'll find Gemma and take her up to the severed floor.
你再指引她去出口楼梯
Where you will guide her to the exit stairwell.
是 好的
Right. Okay.
马克
Mark...
我知道信息量很大 哥们
I know this is a fucking lot, man.
但如果我们能证明她还活着
But if we can prove that she is alive,
如果我们能证明他们绑架了她
if we can prove that they fucking kidnapped her,
就能干掉他们
it will end them.
那我们呢
Well, what happens to us?
什么意思
What do you mean?
如果卢蒙完了 那分离楼层的 所有公司里的自己会怎样
Well, if Lumon ends, then what happens to every innie on the severed floor?
是
Yeah.
- 你希望我牺牲自己  - 不
- You want me to give my life? - No.
牺牲地下的所有人
The lives of everyone down there?
不 不是那么简单
No, it's not that simple.
只为了救出你在意的一个人
Just to save one person you happen to care about?
你不一定要牺牲性命
It doesn't have to end your life.
真的
Really?
对
Right.
其实还有一个人想和你聊
There's somebody else who wants to talk to you, actually.
好 按播放键
Okay, just hit the play.
看完
Watch it.
录下你的回复 然后出去
Record your response, then step outside.
我们就在楼下等你 好吗
We'll just be downstairs, okay?
好的
Okay.
嘿 我...
Hey, I'm...
我想你知道我是谁
Well, I guess you know who I am.
你应该已经和德文 塞尔...
I think you've spoken with Devon and Mrs. Sel...
和科贝尔女士聊过了
Ms. Cobel.
所以你...
So y...
你知道我们希望你做的是什么
you know what it is that we're asking.
但首先 我必须对你说
But the first thing I need to say to you
我很抱歉
is that I am so sorry.
你知道 我创造你出来 你成了囚徒 我的逃避所
You know, I created you as a prisoner and as an escape.
卢蒙告诉我说你会快乐 公司里的自己是满足的
Lumon told me you'd be happy, that innies are content,
我相信他们的话
and because I took their word for it,
所以两年来你生活在噩梦里
you've been living a nightmare for two years.
他们对你做的事是令人发指的
It's horrific what they've done to you.
我在这里的一部分原因是要纠正错误
And part of the reason I'm here is to make it right.
我希望 我们有这么多的共同点
And I hope now with all we have in common,
你会给我这个机会
that you'll give me that chance.
(播放)
嗨
Hi.
哇 这也...我没想过真的会和你对话
Wow, this is... I never expected to actually speak to you.
我的天
Holy shit.
更别说听到你道歉了 所以...
Let alone get an apology, so...
谢谢
Thank you.
你知道 用“噩梦”这个词其实不准确
You know, "nightmare" is the wrong word, actually.
因为我们想到办法去正常过日子 去...
'Cause we find ways to make it work, to...
感到自己是完整的人
to feel whole,
所以你的要求让我害怕
which is why what you're asking scares me.
因为无论这个人生如何
You know, because whatever this life is...
它也是我们仅有的人生
it's all we have,
我们不希望它终结
and we don't want it to end.
你能明白吗
Can you understand that?
我当然能理解
Of course I can.
这一点很有道理
It's such a good point.
如果我是公司里的自己 我也会这么说 但是
I'd say the same thing in your position, however,
你的人生不是非要被卢蒙占满
Lumon doesn't have to be your whole life.
也许最近你会看到一些记忆片段
Now, you may have been seeing flashes lately.
是我在这外面的画面
Images from my world out here.
我也看到了你的记忆片段
I've been seeing yours too.
这是一种叫“恢复记忆”的手术
It's a process called "reintegration."
通过它 记忆重新连接 我们可以再次变成一个人
It's a way to recouple memories so we can be one person.
我开始这个手术是因为 我意识到这一切对你有多不公平
I started this because I see now how unfair this all is to you,
我的妻子自由后 我发誓我会完成手术
and once my wife is free, I swear I will finish the process.
因为这个人生 我们的人生...
'Cause this life, our life...
属于我们两人
belongs to both of us.
我想和你分享
And I wanna share it with you.
好的 但是 实际的结果是什么
Okay. But what would that mean exactly?
意味着右边属于你 左边属于我 还是说...
That you get the right side, and I get the left? Or...
分为上下两半 我...
Is it like a top-bottom situation? I'm--
- 不 - 我真的只是在努力理解
- No. - I'm honestly trying to understand.
不 不是分为上下两半
No, it wouldn't be like a top-bottom situation.
而是两个人一起 就像合为一个人
It's, like, both of us. Like, one person combined.
我的记忆 你的记忆 我的创伤 你的创伤
Like, my memories and yours, and my trauma and yours,
但也有好的东西
but, like, you know, the good stuff too.
好 但...
Okay, but...
你活着的时间比我多20倍
I mean, you've been alive for, what, 20 times longer,
所以无论这个新“合成人”是谁
so whoever this new hybrid person is,
感觉属于你的部分一定比我多得多
it seems like he'd be way more you than me.
我觉得不是这样运作的
I just don't think that's how it works.
好 那是怎样运作
Okay. How does it work?
听着
Look...
两年来 我都在哀悼珍玛
I mourned Gemma for two years.
我失去了工作 我的教职
I lost my job, my teaching job...
因为我会醉醺醺地去学校
because I fucking started showing up drunk.
我把她的东西都藏在地下室
You know, I hid all of her stuff in my basement...
因为假装她从未存在过要更好受
'cause it was easier pretending that she never existed.
我以为我是在保护你 免受那种痛苦
And I thought I was protecting you from that pain.
嘿 科贝尔女士告诉我说 你在下面有心上人
Hey, Ms. Cobel told me you like someone down there?
海伦娜伊根 对吗
Helena Eagan, right?
她公司里的自己好像叫“赫伦妮”
I think her innie name's "Heleny"?
说真的 我很开心你有这份体验
Honestly, I love that you had that experience.
所以 你能想象
So, now you could imagine,
你和赫伦妮之间的感情
like, what you and Heleny have
但是乘以成千上万天的
but multiply, like, thousands of days
快乐 争吵 热情
of, like, joy, and arguments, and passion,
你就能明白为什么我必须找回我的妻子
then you can see why I have to get my wife back.
我必须救她回来
I have to have her back.
其实她叫赫莉...
It's Helly, actually. Helly.
我爱上她了
It's the person I'm in love with,
如果你过去曾对我的人生 好奇一点 就会知道
which you'd know if you'd ever taken an interest in my life.
今晚你的好奇只因为你对我有需要
Before tonight, when you need something.
如果我按你说的做 我就会失去她
She's the person I'll lose if I do what you say
因为你和我一样很清楚 她公司外的自己不会恢复记忆
'cause you know as well as I do that her outie won't, like, reintegrate,
我这是假设所谓的恢复记忆是真的
assuming that's even real.
假设你嘴里的话不都是假的
Assuming every word outta your mouth isn't a lie.
什...
Wha...
对不起 我不是有意...
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to...
哥们 我只是想救妻子 好吗
Dude, I'm just trying to save my wife, okay?
我不能抛下她 如果你帮助我
I mean, I can't abandon her, and if you help me,
我也不会抛下你 我保证
I won't abandon you. I promise.
你知道我是怎么想的吗  我认为你救回妻子后
You know what I think? I think the second you get your wife back,
立马就会忘记我存在过
you forget I ever existed.
我认为我会和地下 所有公司里的自己一起消失
I think that I disappear along with every innie down there.
你对我有什么要求
What do you want from me?
我们是一条船上的
We are in this together.
你就不能信我一回
Can't you just trust me?
不能
No.
德文
Devon!
他是个小屁孩 他不肯听
He's a fucking child. He won't listen.
我来和他谈
Let me speak to him.
我说到恢复记忆 他根本不相信
I mentioned reintegration, he basically called bullshit.
他也不算错 对吧
Well, he's not wrong, right?
我来和他谈
Let me speak to him.
单独谈
Alone.
好的 行
Okay. Yeah.
好
Okay.
那些数字是你的妻子
The numbers are your wife.
宏观数据精检的数字
The MDR numbers.
你主机上的那些
From your console.
它们是进入珍玛斯科特大脑的通道 也就是你外面自己的妻子
They're a doorway into the mind of your outie's wife, Gemma Scout.
我不懂
I don't understand.
你每天看着数字时 看见了什么
What do you see every day when you look at them?
什...我们有一些感受
What... we feel things.
你有什么感受
What do you feel?
不同的感受 有时是悲伤
Different things. Sometimes sadness...
悲哀
Woe.
嬉笑
Frolic.
恶意
Malice.
恐惧
Dread.
所以你的意思是...
So you're saying the...
数字群是...
the clusters are...
她的脾气
Her tempers.
是她大脑的建构基础
The building blocks of her mind.
我在建造什么
What am I building?
你完成的每一份文件
Every file you've completed...
(塔姆沃特)
都是她的一个新的意识
is a new consciousness for her.
(威灵顿)
(德兰斯维尔)
(阿伦敦)
一个新的公司里的自己
A new innie.
我完成了24个文件
I've completed 24 files.
冷港是最后一个
Cold Harbor is the last.
明天是你在卢蒙的最后一天
Tomorrow will be your final day at Lumon.
到时你便完成了自己的使命 她也是
You will have served your purpose, and so will she.
等等 你为什么要告诉我
Wait, why are you telling me this?
你来这到底是为什么
What are you doing here, really?
马克...
Mark. Mark.
你和赫莉R不会拥有好的结局
There'll be no honeymoon ending for you and Helly R.
她是伊根家族的人
She's an Eagan.
你对他们来说一文不值
You're nothing to them.
- 不 - 对她来说一文不值
- No. - Nothing to her.
不 我不相信你
No, I don't believe you.
他们在利用你
They're using you.
不 我不相信你
No! I don't believe you!
然后他们会像对待废茧衣一样抛弃你
Then they'll discard you like a skin husk.
- 我觉得你在利用我 - 马克
- I think you're using me! - Mark!
- 恢复记忆是你唯一的机会 - 等等
- Reintegration is your only chance! - Wait.
- 你爱你哥哥吗  - 马克
- Do you love your brother? - Mark!
爱
Yes.
那就告诉他 我睁开眼看到的
Well, then you tell him that the next thing I see
最好是分离楼层
had better be the severed floor,
否则他别想再见到他的妻子
or I swear he will never see his wife again.
我在乎你
I care for you.
别说了
Stop!
马克
Mark.
我要告诉你一件事
I have to tell you something.
我也是
Me too.
老天啊
Fuck me.
(马克S)
“马克 创始人期盼目睹 你完成第25份文件的历史性一刻
"Mark, The Founder wished to witness the historic completion of your 25th file.
赫莉R也会在自己的座位上见证
Helly R. shall also bear witness from her chair.
你的胜利将伴随着美好的辉煌 米尔奇克先生上”
Goodly splendors await upon your victory. Love, Mr. Milchick."
(卢蒙)
(冷港)
杰姆伊根来过
Jame Eagan was here.
他来找我
He came to see me.
他说了一些神神秘秘的话 什么在我身上看到基尔之火
He said some cryptic shit about the fire of Kier being in me,
说今天是特别的日子
and that today is a special day.
我知道原因
I know why.
我知道他们做这些的原因
I know why they're doing this.
你好 迪伦
Hello, Dylan.
他拒绝了
He said no?
跟我来
Follow me.
(冷港的辉煌胜利)
所以他们取出芯片后会发生什么
So, what happens when they extract the chip?
我们怎能相信科贝尔说的话
But how can we trust anything Cobel says?
她从不说真话
All she's ever done is lie.
我知道 但这次她看起来不同了
I know, but she seemed different.
她还是那个人 但是感觉有些不同
I mean, she's the same, but, like, different same.
我不知道
I don't know.
(冷港 完成进度:96%)
我可以选择不做
I mean, I could just not do it.
我可以不完成文件 不救她出来
I could just not finish the file, not get her out.
但如果她说的是真话 那我们无论如何都完蛋
But if she's telling the truth, we're screwed either way.
现在什么情况
What's happening?
穿衣服
Just get dressed.
一切都会好好的
Everything is gonna be fine.
但如果你救她出去 也许能扳倒卢蒙 就像他妹妹说的
But if you get her out, maybe that will take down Lumon, like his sister said.
也许你们可以“合二为一”
And maybe you can do this combining thing.
是 但也许他是个大骗子
Well, yeah, but he could be a total liar.
如果他不是呢
What if he's not?
至少你有机会活下去
At least you'll have a chance at living.
是 但我想和你一起活下去
Yeah, but I wanna live with you.
但我是她 马克
But I'm her, Mark.
我是她
I'm her.
好的
Okay.
(完成进度:97%)
你外面的自己回应了你的辞职请求
Your outie has responded to your resignation request.
鉴于这可能导致你产生 令你难堪的情绪反应
As it may yield an embarrassing emotional response in you,
也由于我有多个要务在身
and as I'm duly swamped,
我将让你独自阅读
I shall leave you to read it in solitude.
(公司里的自己辞职申请)
(外面的自己回复)
“亲爱的公司里的自己
"Dear innie,
我读了你的申请 并将我的回复 分为三个要点
I've read your request and organized my response into three points.
第一点:去死吧”
Point one: fuck you."
格雷琴是我的妻子和一生挚爱
Gretchen is my wife and my beloved,
你对她做的举动纯属毫不知耻
and your actions with her were deeply fucking indecorous.
第二点
Point two:
我懂的
I get it.
她很完美 鉴于你我生理机能一样 你一定也同意
She's perfect, and given our shared physiology, it tracks that you'd agree.
问题来了
Here's the thing.
我这辈子都不是什么厉害的人物
I've never been an impressive person,
所以当格雷琴说你是个充满自信的猛人时
so when Gretch told me that you're, like, this self-assured badass,
怎么说呢
I don't know.
我挺受伤的
It stung.
所以 这是第三点
So I guess, point three is:
我希望有一天她能像欣赏你一样欣赏我
I hope someday she sees in me what she sees in you.
此外 我说实话
In the meantime, if I'm being really honest,
知道公司里存在这个你 我挺开心的
I guess I like knowing you're there.
所以如果你想走 你可以走
So if you wanna leave, you can.
但我觉得你应该留下
But I think you should stay.
真诚敬上 你外面的自己
Sincerest regards, Your outie.
(完成进度:99%)
我在想有没有除了特拉华之外的其他地名
Been trying to think of other place names besides Delaware.
我想到了欧洲 津巴布韦...
I've got Europe, Zimbabwe...
赤道
and the Equator.
The Equator?
是一栋楼吗
Is that a building?
或是一个大陆
Or a continent.
也许是一栋楼 太大了...
Maybe it's just a building that's, like, so big...
变成了大陆
That it became a continent.
是
Yeah.
我只是希望我们有更多时间
I just wish we had more time.
至少我们拥有过的是快乐的
Least it's a happy one.
打给伊根先生
Call Mr. Eagan.
马克S
Mark S.,
鉴于你完成了第25份宏观数据文件
in completing your 25th Macrodata file,
我的宏伟计划更接近实现
you have drawn my grand agendum nearer to fulfillment,
因此 你成为
thus making you
历史上最重要的人之一
one of the most important people in history.
请享受你兢兢业业的成果
Revel now in the fruit of your labors,
并致敬你在尘世的管理者
and hail your earthbound steward,
也就是你的...
your very own...
楼层主管
floor manager!
谢谢您 基尔
Thank you, Kier.
我也想说 您非常英俊 先生
And may I say, you're looking very handsome, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
我也想回你同样的话
I'd say the same of you,
只是我要遵从最爱的核心原则
if not for my favorite core principle.
诚实
Probity?
不
No.
视野
Vision.
我实感荣幸 能招待如此杰出
Well, it's truly special to host a man so illustrious,
如此睿智 如此宽宏...
so sapient, so magnanimous--
你真爱掉书袋
My, you're verbose.
还好附录一不是你写的
Good thing you didn't write the first appendix.
否则会装不下
It would've burst.
很荣幸能被您打趣 伊根先生
It's an honor to receive your barbs, Mr. Eagan.
您留给后世的传承 真真正正 无可置疑地超越尘世
The legacy you've left behind is truly and irrefutably larger than life.
你是说我的公司
You mean my company?
不
No.
我是说这一座比你真人要高13厘米的蜡像
I mean this wax statue that's five inches taller than you actually were.
谢谢你的评论
Thank you for that feedback...
塞斯
Seth.
谢谢您 基尔
Thank you, Kier.
现在 宏观数据精检的各位女士 先生
And now, lady and gentleman of MDR,
有请舞蹈和娱乐部
may I introduce Choreography and Merriment!
走吧
Let's go.
(舞蹈娱乐)
马克
Mark!
欢迎 伊根先生
Welcome, Mr. Eagan.
效用测试将很快开始
The efficacy test will begin shortly.
(测试即将开始)
谢谢你们 舞蹈娱乐部
Thank you, C&M.
让我们继续为马克S庆祝...
Let's keep the Mark S. love going...
我得走了
I have to leave.
请欣赏安布罗斯
...with the Ballad of Ambrose
和甘诺尔抒情曲
and Gunnel.
准备了
You ready?
是
Yeah.
我们赤道见
See you at the Equator.
赤道见
嘿 能帮帮我吗
Hey. Can I get a little help?
(冷港)
嘿
Hey!
能帮帮我吗
Can I get a little help here?
赫莉
Helly.
马克在哪
Where's Mark?
我不知道
I don't know!
- 嘿 - 是
- Hey. - Yeah.
进房间
Enter the room.
你是谁
Who are you?
我不知道
I don't know.
哺乳动物培育部送来了一只供品
Mammalians Nurturable brings an offering.
有活力吗
Has it verve?
有的
It does.
狡黠
Wiles?
是它这一群中最狡黠的
The most of its flock.
这只野兽将与一位可贵的女人埋葬在一起
This beast will be entombed with a cherished woman,
它必须指引她的精神找到基尔
whose spirit it must guide to Kier's door.
它有能力完成这项任务吗
Is it up to the task?
有的
It is.
那就把它的生命给我
Then give me its life.
拆了它
Take it apart.
赫莉
Helly!
不好意思
Excuse me.
我们将这只动物献给基尔
We commit this animal to Kier,
以及他向痛苦发起的永久抗战
and his eternal war against pain.
多少
How many?
多少什么
How many what?
我还要给多少只
How many more must I give?
创始者要多少就给多少
As many as the Founder calls.
马克S
Mark S.
走错门了
Wrong door.
我这就离开 好吗
I'm leaving, okay?
噢 糟糕
Oh, fuck.
别再杀生了
No more killing.
等等...
Wait, wait, wait!
别开枪...
Wait! Wait.
求求你...
Please. Please. Please.
屏障仍在生效
The barrier is holding.
她什么都感觉不到
She feels nothing.
真美
It's beautiful.
谢谢
Thank you.
埃米尔感谢你
Emile thanks you.
埃米尔是这只山羊的名字
Emile is the name of the goat.
好吧
Okay.
好的
一秒后 我会变成外面的自己
Now, in a second I'm gonna change to my outie,
你要带他去...
and then you are gonna take him to--
(明斯克)
(塔姆沃特)
你干吗
What are you doing?
这是舞蹈和娱乐部的乐器
Those instruments are property of Choreography and Merriment.
(阿德莱德)
舞蹈和娱乐部 立即回到你们的部门
Choreography and Merriment, return to your department now!
撤回舞蹈娱乐部 我们的表演受到干扰了
Fall back to C&M. Our performance has been compromised.
不...等等...
No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait.
等等
Wait.
这张桌子过去有四个座位
This desk used to have four seats.
我们的朋友欧文走了
Our friend Irving is gone,
他们要除掉我们整个部门
and they want our whole department gone.
如果他逃出来 我们会死
If he gets out, we're dead.
他们要把我们关掉 就像该死的机器
They're gonna turn us off like fucking machines.
你也见过他们这样做的
You've seen them do it.
我知道你们也失去过朋友
I know you've lost friends too.
也许下一个就是你
And you could be next.
也许下一个是你
You could be next.
他们给我们半个人生 以为我们不会为之抗争
They give us half a life and think we won't fight for it.
(冷港)
米尔奇克 对吗
Right, Milchick?
拜托 帮帮我们
Please, help us.
拜托
Please.
帮帮我们
Help us.
- 你是怎么进来的  - 老天
- How did you get in here? - Jesus.
打开门
Open the door.
- 滚远点 混蛋 - 开门
- Step off, fucko. - Do it.
- 不... - 现在 给我开门 快开...
- No! No! No! No! No! - Now. Do it! Go! Go!
不...你去死...
No! No, fuck you! Fuck you!
不 毛厄医生 去你的
No! Dr. Mauer! Fuck you!
天啊 该死
Jesus. Fuck.
珍玛
Gemma?
没事的 是我
It's okay. It's me.
我是你的丈夫
I'm your husband.
好
Okay.
你叫珍玛斯科特
Your name is Gemma Scout.
我们结婚四年了
We'd been married for four years.
不
No.
我们...
We were...
我们曾有美好的生活
We had a life together...
别和那个男人说话
Don't speak to that man.
他是来伤害你的
He's here to hurt you.
如果你现在跟我走 我们可以找回曾经的生活
And if you come with me right now, we can get it back.
不
No.
停下
Stop.
这不是测试的一部分
This is not a part of the test.
- 拜托 - 别让他碰你
- Please. - Don't let him touch you.
我们必须离开
We have to go.
停下
Stop!
噢 糟糕
Oh, fuck.
达蒙德先生...该死
Mr. Drummond. Mr. Drummond. Damn!
没事的
It's okay.
该死的
Fuck!
是她的丈夫
It's the fucking spouse!
打给达蒙德先生
Call Drummond!
好的 你可以过来 别怕
Okay. You can come. It's okay.
来
Come on.
来吧
出来吧
Come on out.
没事的
It's okay.
马克
Mark.
快走
Come on.
珍玛
Gemma!
珍玛 停下
Gemma. Stop!
不...
No, no, no.
不
No.
你会杀死他们所有人的
You'll kill them all!
马克S
Mark S.?
凯西女士
Ms. Casey.
发生了什么
What's taking place?
走吧
Come on.
好的 来吧
Okay. Come on.
好的
Okay.
- 你必须现在离开 走吧 - 去哪
- You have to go right now. Go. - Where?
快 你必须立即离开
Come on! You gotta go right now!
快走
Go.
去你的 米尔奇克先生
Fuck you, Mr. Milchick.
马克...快来
Mark. Mark, come on.
来啊 马克
Come on, Mark.
快来 我们必须走了
Come on. We have to go.
马克...开开门 拜托
Mark! Mark, open the door. Come on.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
开门
Open the door.
马克 我们得回家
Mark, we gotta go home.
马克
Mark.
马克 快啊 马克 开门
Mark, come on. Mark, open the door.
马克 你必须来 开门 快点啊
Mark, you have to come. Open the door. Come on.
马克
Mark.
Mark!
马克
什么 马克
What? Mark!
马克...
Mark! Mark!
该死 马克 我们必须离开这里
Goddamn it, Mark, we have to get out of here.
马克...我们必须离开这里
Mark! Mark! We have to get out of here!
马克...我们得走了
Mark! Mark, we gotta go.
马克
Mark.
马克...不...马克
Mark! Mark, no. No. Mark.
马克
Mark.
马克 开门啊 马克
Mark! Open the door! Mark!
不 马克
No! Mark!
马克 回来
Mark! Come back!
马克
Mark!